export const AlphaQuestions = [
    {
      name: 'Christmas Cinemoji',
      rows: [
        {points: 100, question: 'Characters:\n💀🐶🧵\n🔊🐛🎅', size: '20vh', answer: 'Nightmare Before Christmas'}, //nightmare before christmas
        {points: 200, question: 'Title:\n☠️💎', size: '25vh', answer: 'Die Hard'}, // Die Hard
        {points: 300, question: 'Props:\n🌝♿💸🎄🔔', size: '25vh', answer: "It's a Wonderful Life"}, //It's a wonderful life
        {points: 400, question: 'Scenes:\n👅🦵🧼🏈🦆', size: '22vh', answer:'A Christmas Story'}, //A Christmas Story
        {points: 500, question: 'Plot:\n💈🚕🎅📨🎶👶', size: '22vh', answer: 'Elf'}, //Elf
      ]
    },
    {
      name: 'Yultide Lyrics',
      rows: [
        {points: 100, question: 'Tiny tots with their eyes all aglow', size: '20vh', answer: 'The Christmas Song'}, //The Christmas Song
        {points: 200, question: 'I wanna wish you a Merry Christmas', size: '20vh', answer: 'Feliz Navidad'}, //Feliz Navidad
        {points: 300, question: 'From angels bending near the earth /\nTo touch their harps of gold', size: '15vh', answer: 'It Came Upon the Midnight Clear'}, //It came upon the midnight clear
        {points: 400, question: 'She\'s candy apple red with a ski for a wheel', size: '20vh', answer: 'Little Saint Nick'}, //Little Saint Nick
        {points: 500, question: 'Voices singing,\nLet\'s be jolly', size: '21vh', answer: 'Rocking Around the Christmas Tree'}, //Rocking around the christmas tree
      ]
    },
    {
      name: 'Holiday Hodgepodge',
      rows: [
        {points: 100, question: "A comet, a conjunction,\nand a 'hypernova' are all hypothetical origins of this bilical nativity spectacle. ", size: '15vh', answer: 'The Star of Bethlehem'}, // star of bethlehem
        {points: 200, question: 'Cookies and candies fill children\'s clogs in this European country.', size: '20vh', answer: 'The Netherlands'}, //Netherlands
        {points: 300, question: 'The common names of the Magi in Western church tradition are Balthazar of Arabia, Caspar of India, and _____ of Persia.', size: '13.5vh', answer: 'Melchior'}, //Melchior
        {points: 400, question: 'Only one ____ in the\nwhole world, joked\nJohnny Carson on this dessert.', size: '16vh', answer: 'Fruitcake'}, //fruitcake
        {points: 500, question: 'Originally an Irish Catholic tradition, this welcoming illumination for travellers and neighbors is now a classic.', size: '14vh', answer: 'A candle in the window'},
      ]
    }
  ];

export const QuestionSet2 = [
  {
    name: 'Christmas Cinemoji',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: 'Plot:\n🎅🦷⛏️🌨️🔴', size: '20vh', answer: 'Rudolph the Red Nose Reindeer'}, 
      {points: 200, question: 'Title (sounds like):\n📅❌🏜️🦀', size: '22vh', answer: 'Year Without a Sandy Claws'}, 
      {points: 300, question: 'Props:\n⏰🍕📼🚂🕷️', size: '22vh', answer: "Home Alone"},
      {points: 400, question: 'Scenes:\n⛰️🐶🍖🎄🎁', size: '22vh', answer:'How the Grinch Stole Christmas'},
      {points: 500, question: 'Plot:\n🦃👴👊⚖️💌🏡', size: '22vh', answer: 'Miracle on 34th St'},
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Yultide Lyrics',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: "And everyone is singing\n(oh, yeah)\nI hear those sleigh bells ringing (Oh)", size: '14vh', answer: 'All I Want For Christmas Is You'}, 
      {points: 200, question: "Dolls that will talk and will go for a walk \/\nIs the hope of Janice and Jen;", size: '14vh', answer: "It's Beginning to Look a Lot Like Christmas"}, 
      {points: 300, question: "It'll nearly be like a\npicture print \/\nBy Currier and Ives", size: '16vh', answer: 'Sleigh Ride'}, 
      {points: 400, question: "And there it did both stop and stay \/\nRight over the place where Jesus lay.", size: '16vh', answer: 'The First Noel'}, 
      {points: 500, question: "Hurry down the chimney tonight \/\nHurry, tonight", size: '18vh', answer: 'Santa Baby'}, 
    ]
  },
  {
    name: 'Holiday Hodgepodge',
    rows: [
      {points: 100, question: "Which one of Santa's reindeer has the same name as another holiday mascot?", size: '15vh', answer: 'Cupid'}, 
      {points: 200, question: "What did my true love give to me on the eighth day of Christmas?", size: '15vh', answer: '8 Maids a Milking'}, 
      {points: 300, question: "Stars, needle, plate, dendrite, column, lacy, and capped column are the six main types of what?", size: '15vh', answer: 'Snowflakes'}, 
      {points: 400, question: "Which incredibly popular Christmas song was originally written for Thanksgiving in 1857?", size: '15vh', answer: 'Jingle Bells'}, 
      {points: 500, question: "In which modern-day country was the canonical Saint Nicholas born in?", size: '15vh', answer: 'Turkey (Lycia, Asia Minor)'}
    ]
  }
]